Rumeng, where did you run off to?
My dad put me under house arrest at home.
Your dad put you under house arrest?
Mm.
Hurry and come save me.
Where should I go to save you?
Baixia Road 09-02
Get here fast.
Youyou, I have an outfit—see if it fits you.
Clothes?
Mm.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What clothes?
Come in and try it.
Come in and try.
Sis.
Open the door.
Xu Rumeng, open the door!
Quick!
Shh.
We'll talk outside.
Go.
Go, quickly.
Nanfeng.
I don't want to go to the set anymore.
Why?
Director Du already agreed to make you the Female lead.
What a great opportunity.
Haven't you always wanted to take this path?
Nanfeng.
Can we leave Shengang
and not go back to Haicheng
We'll find a
place where no one knows us
and start over, okay?
You're being too willful.
Nanfeng.
I...
Rumeng.
I owe Zhiyi too much.
I originally thought
it was heaven giving me a chance to start over
But
no matter what,
I don't want to hurt you
or deceive you
The two of us
let's leave it at that.
I hope you can understand me.
I won't.
Alright.
We've been out too long.
It'll be dark by the time we get back.
Let me take you back.
We're home.
Go on in.
Mm.
Umbrella.
Rumeng.
Dad knows
this is really shameful,
but for your happiness,
don't blame Dad.
I've arranged everything you instructed.
Uncle, something's wrong!
My sister is missing.
She's gone.
Didn't I tell you to watch her?
I...
didn't keep an eye on her.
Have you looked?
We did.
We couldn't find her.
Go find her, now!
What is going on?
I...
What's wrong?
Chairman Xu.
You really have some nerve, Zheng Nanfeng!
You dare bully my daughter?
I...
Why am I here?
Sis.
So you two made up?
No.
What's going on?
This is outrageous!
You are outrageous!
Hurry up and put some clothes on.
I originally thought
you were a promising young man
I never imagined you would do something like this
No, Chairman Xu
I was just bringing Rumeng back
Then I was going to
Then
Then you took her to the bed
No
There may be a misunderstanding
What misunderstanding
So many people are here
We saw it with our own eyes
How could that be false
Boss
On the CCTV, it has already
recorded him climbing into the villa
You snuck over the wall into my home
What were you after
What else do you have to say
By doing this
you've ruined my Rumeng's reputation
You must take responsibility
Dad, don't force him
Stay out of this
Dad will handle it for you
If you do not give an explanation today
I will not let you off
Zheng Nanfeng
Why one story in the morning and another at night
What are you really thinking
Rumeng, I truly do not know
what is going on
It is a fact you climbed over the wall
Stop quibbling
Keep a close eye on him
If there is no explanation
do not even think of leaving my house
Yes
Dad, you cannot do this
You go back to your room too
Do not come out without my orders
Youyou, take your sister back to her room
If she runs off again
do not come to see me anymore
Uncle
Uncle, bad news
What happened
Rumeng ran off again
It is not about my sister
The company's E-commerce Project was halted
Halted
How was it halted
This project
Half the board voted against
In Silicon Valley
are there not already success stories
The E-commerce Project
will surely replace physical merchants
We should be the first to take the plunge
This is a key strategic project
It has tremendous prospects
We should push it forward
Why would they vote against
They said they did a risk assessment
They said the project's risk is too high
Let me see
E-commerce
Online shopping
They are already building an online shopping platform
Nonsense
It is utter nonsense
Uncle
So what should we do now
Go
Convene the board and reassess
What if they gang up at the meeting
We need a contingency plan in advance
Chairman Xu
Maybe I can help with this
This is the latest from America
E-commerce Project
There is no domestic precedent
You
do not meddle
How is that meddling blindly
E-commerce can solve many
problems in remote transactions
Think long term
Just imagine
You place an order at home on a mobile phone today
and it is delivered to your door the next day
Isn't that convenient
What is a mobile phone
It is like the brick phone we use now
just with a few more features
I did not expect you knew about this
This is just the start
Well
I will take a look at the project proposal first
I know where your project’s risk points are
I can help optimize your project workflow
and reduce the risk level
Youyou
Notify them
Hold an emergency board meeting this afternoon
Okay, Uncle
Rumeng
Dad
How did your meeting go?
The board approved it unanimously
The E-commerce Project officially launched
Initial funding of 100 million
Zheng Nanfeng will serve as CEO
Youyou will be Director of the R&D Department
He will be CEO
The business model proposed by Zheng Nanfeng
breaks old barriers
Truly a business genius!
I used to think you were just a screenwriter
I did not expect that
you are also so skilled with the internet
This cross-over of yours
is a bit too reckless
Well, I only proposed a broad concept
As for how the project will operate in detail,
that is up to our chief engineer
Where is Xu Youyou?
Sis
From now on, my brother-in-law and I
will be a Dynamic Duo
Anyway,
you made a big contribution to the company this time
Go ahead,
what reward do you want?
Actually, it is nothing, Chairman Xu
Just…
From now on, could you stop having these two big guys
follow me wherever I go?
Hahaha
I will just be frank with you
This is also my personal wish
I see Rumeng likes you so much
and I think highly of you
so
I want
you to be my son-in-law
I miss you
Whenever dusk falls
the evening breeze blows
I miss you
Life’s riddle
Try not to see it clearly
Close your eyes
Do not respond
The evening wind blows and blows
Go with the wind
Tonight, kids, do not cry in secret
Do not cry in secret
The evening wind blows and blows
Go with the wind
As the starry night falls
Gently fall asleep
Feel the evening breeze